Finally,
let's review the steps to create a case.
Add notes and then close the case to thoroughly document the interaction.
Navigate to the new inquiry panel from
within the newly created prospective member record.
Create a new case using programs and services as the type,
and EMSU as the subtype.
Then click Add Next
and done to finish creating the case.
A new case will open with an in progress status and will be given a case number.
Next,
add case notes.
In the notes section of the case,
select the option to add a new note.
Then add details in the body text field.
Keep your notes simple.
For example,
transferred caller to EMSU.
After adding your note,
click done to save it to the case record.
Finally,
close the case using the Close case action button
in the upper right corner of the screen.
In the resolution reason pop-up,
choose Call Transferred,
then click Close.
The case will be closed and the unknown
call will be documented as transferred to EMSU.